[{"Question":"The boy ____ came to see me this morning had come from Agra.","option 1":"which","option 2":"who","option 3":" that","option 4":"whom","answer":"who"},{"Question":"You _____ be mad if you think Iâ€™m going to lend you any more money.","option 1":" might","option 2":" should","option 3":" ought to","option 4":"must","answer":"must"},{"Question":"Having ______ in both government and private schools, Palak is the most suitable person to take over as the principal of the school.","option 1":"works","option 2":"working","option 3":"worked","option 4":"was working","answer":"worked"},{"Question":"The rotten smell was so _________ that she became unconscious then and there and had to be hospitalized.","option 1":"revolting","option 2":"gratifying","option 3":"captivating","option 4":"unappealing","answer":"revolting"},{"Question":"Single-use plastic refers to the entire class of items that are used once and then _____ of.","option 1":" thought","option 2":" excluded","option 3":"abandoned","option 4":"disposed","answer":"disposed"},{"Question":"Yesterday, the villagers caught a burglar _______ a bottle of oil from the community hall.","option 1":"embezzling","option 2":"frauding","option 3":"swindling","option 4":"pilfering","answer":"pilfering"},{"Question":"Right now, the concern is about banks not lowering their lending rates fast enough, ______ the repo rate has been coming down.","option 1":"because","option 2":"since","option 3":"although","option 4":"from","answer":"although"},{"Question":"Smoking will never be given up, _____ the tobacco industry thrives.","option 1":" so that","option 2":"as long as","option 3":" though","option 4":"as if","answer":"as long as"},{"Question":"Are you looking forward ____ Akhil again?","option 1":"seeing","option 2":"to see","option 3":" to be seeing","option 4":" to seeing","answer":" to seeing"},{"Question":"He _____ a lot of letters yesterday.","option 1":" had written","option 2":"had been writing","option 3":"wrote","option 4":" has written","answer":"wrote"},{"Question":"Banks should be left free to set their lending rates, in ______ with their cost of funds and market conditions, apart from borrower profile.","option 1":" lending","option 2":" meeting","option 3":"settling","option 4":"accordance","answer":"accordance"},{"Question":"The police commissioner condemned the _________ murder and vowed to apprehend the wrongdoers within a fortnight.","option 1":"grisly","option 2":"gruesome","option 3":"All of the above","option 4":"ghastly","answer":"All of the above"},{"Question":"The ________ apparition stalked Reshma for days and ultimately threw her off the cliff.","option 1":" vindictive","option 2":"benevolent","option 3":"magnanimous","option 4":"callous","answer":" vindictive"},{"Question":"A heavy storm was forecast _____ the weather was clear.","option 1":"but","option 2":"because","option 3":"unless","option 4":"and","answer":"but"},{"Question":"If he had gone to Agra, he _____ the Taj Mahal.","option 1":"have been seen","option 2":"had been seen","option 3":" saw","option 4":"would have seen","answer":"would have seen"},{"Question":"It will make a bad economic situation marginally ______ and, perhaps, even create a black market in certain articles.","option 1":"good","option 2":"worse","option 3":"better","option 4":"weaker","answer":"worse"},{"Question":"Indiaâ€™s problem is not the paucity of traffic rules and regulations but a general ______ for them.","option 1":" insistence","option 2":"absence","option 3":"allocation","option 4":" disregard","answer":" disregard"},{"Question":"The Mekong is also home ______ the worldâ€™s largest catfish.","option 1":" for","option 2":"in","option 3":"within","option 4":" to","answer":" to"},{"Question":"They ______________ her and trusted her for years","option 1":"know","option 2":"knew","option 3":"had known","option 4":"known","answer":"knew"},{"Question":"Every morning she ______________ up early and gets ready for work.","option 1":"is waking","option 2":"has woken","option 3":"had woken","option 4":"wakes","answer":"wakes"}]
